Guide to the Cornell University Library Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections records
Cornell University Library Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Library Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections records.
13-1-1084
Cornell University Library. Office of the Assistant Director for the Development of Collections
23.8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files, and records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Correspondence, subject files, and records of library acquisitions kept by Dr. Felix Reichmann, Assistant Director.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, subject files, and records of library acquisitions kept by Dr. Felix Reichmann, Assistant Director.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University Library.; Reichmann, Felix, 1899-
Subjects:
Libraries--Acquisitions--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collections #13-1-720 and #13-1-898.
CONTAINER LIST
- General Correspondence, A-C, 1951-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A[ssociation] C[ollege] R[esearch] L[ibraries] Microcard Series, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Adelmann, Howard, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- African Acquisitions thru 1958, 1952-1953; 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- American Acquisitions thru 1958, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Asia Acquisitions thru 1958, 1952; 1955, (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Associations and Committees: ALA, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Associations and Committees - ALA: Out of Print Book Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Associations and Committees: A.C.R.L, 1951-1953; 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Associations and Committees: A.R.L., 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Associations and Committees: A.R.L., 1953; 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Australian Acquisitions thru 1958, 1952; 1954,; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Canada Acquisitions thru 1958, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CUL Archives, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- General - Columbia University - pre 1958, 1952-1953; 1955, (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cornell University Libraries - Book Fund, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cornell University Library Departmental (A-Z misc.), 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Libraries - Departmental Whetzel, 1952-1954; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cornell Unievrsity Libraries - Departmental Buisness, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Cornell Unievrsity Libraries - Departmental Music, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CUL: Dissertations, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cornell University Libraries - I.L.R., 1951-1953; 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- CUL - F. Reichmann: Report on European Trip and Articles about It, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Libraries - Mann, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cornell University Libraries - Memos, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell University Libraries - Main Acquisitions Dept. - Memos, etc., 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cornell University Libraries - Main Cataloging Dept., 1953; 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cornell University Libraries - Main Rare Books Dept., 1951-1954; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cornell University Libraries - Main Serials and Binding Dept., 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Libraries - Periodicals, Serials Doc., 1947; 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- CUL - Policies and Procedures, 1947; 1953-1954,; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- CUL - Staff Memoranda, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CUL - Want Lists - thru 1958, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- General Correspondence D-I thru 1958, 1951-1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Emanuel, Victor, 1953; 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Misc. European Acquisitions thru 1958, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- European Acquisitions - England - to 1958, 1952-1955; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- European Acquisitions - France - thru 1958, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- European Acquisitions - Germany - thru 1958, 1951-1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Farmington Plan. Correspondence, etc., 1952-1953; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Germany: Heidelberg, 1951-1952; 1954,; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Gifts thru 1958, 1953-1954; 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Acquisitions - Italy thru 1958, 1953; 1957-[1958] (Box 2, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence D-N thru 1958, 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1951-1955; 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- General - University of Michigan pre 1958, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Monthly Reports - Acquisitions Dept., 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- N[ew] Y[ork] S[tate] L[ibrary] A[ssociation], 1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence O-S thru 1958, 1952-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Pending - CUL offers to others, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Pending - Deferred offers (Misc.), re Acquisitions (Box 2, Folder 9)
- General - University of Pennsylvania pre 1958, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Philippines Acquisitions thru 1958, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Research Club, 1959; 1961-1962,; 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Roiser, James, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Russian Acquisitions thru 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Southeast Asia Program - General - thru 1958, 1951-1956; 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- SEA: Burma, 1952-1953; 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- SEA: Burma, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- SEA: Burma - Silverstein, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- SEA: Cambodia - Laos - Vietnam, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- SEA: Indonesia, Acquisitons, Correspondence, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- SEA: Indonesia Kantor Pusat Statistik, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- SEA: Indonesia: Jajasan Pembanunan, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- SEA: Malaya, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- SEA: Thai Cataloguing, 1955; 1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- SEA: Thailand Acquisitions and Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Geneal Correspondence T-Z thru 1958, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Tech[nical] Serv[ice] Adm[inistration] - Archives, 1955; [1960-1963] (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Techincal Services Directors Charts, etc., 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Technical Services: LC. Statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- General - U.S. Governmnet pre 1958, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- U.S. Acquisitions A-Z pre 1958, 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- General - Yale University pre 1958, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Holland Land Co. Microfilming Project, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Israel thru 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- General - A, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- African Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Allen, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- America's Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ALA Series, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Asia Research Center, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Australian Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Australian Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Europe, Misc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Genreal - B, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Book and Bowl, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Re Budget, Funds, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Buffalo, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- General - C, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Canada, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Cornell University - Misc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Re Classification, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Cornell University Library, Misc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- C[ornell] U[niversity] L[ibraries], Re Procedures, Reports, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Personnel, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Memos, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- General D-E-F, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Prof. Echols, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- England, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- France, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- General G-H-I, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Germany, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Gift, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Harrassowitz, Jan. 1959-June 1959 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Harrassowitz, July 1959-Dec. 1959 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Israel, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Italy, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- General J-K-L, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Kraus, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Latin America - Kurtz Mission, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Latin America - Kurtz Mission, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Library of Congress, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Library of Congress - Cataloguing in Sources, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- General - M, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Microcard, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Microfilm - Foreign, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Microfilm - U.S., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Music Committee, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- General - N, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Nardecchia, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Nijhoff, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Netherlands, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- N[ew] Y[ork] L[ibrary] A[ssociation], 1959 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- General - O-P, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Pennsylvania State Univ. Library, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Philippines, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- General - Q-R, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- F[elix] R[eichmann] - Personal, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Re Sugar, Gold, Coffee, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Reichmann: sugar, gold, coffee, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Russian Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Le Livre Etranger - Russian, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Russian - Micro, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- General - S, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Southeast Asian Acquisitions - Misc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- India, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Indonesia, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Japan, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ralph Shaw - Money, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Stechert - Hafner, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- General - T, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Tice, Lynch, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- U.S. Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- U.S. Acquisitions, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- U.S. Acquisitions - D-H, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- U.S. Acquisitions - I-L, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- U.S. Acquisitions - M, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- U.S. Acquisitions - N-R, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- U.S. Acquisitions - S, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- U.S. Acquisitions - T-Z, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Andrew D. White - Diary, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- General - V-Z, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Acquisitions Section: Acquisitions Policy and Research Committee, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- ALA Midwinter Meeting, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Monthly Meeting - Dept. Heads, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Annual Report, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Annual Report of the Acquisitions Librarian, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Asian Acq. - Burma, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Asian Acq. - Hong Kong, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Asian Acq. - India, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- General - A, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- African Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Allen, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Australian Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- General - B, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Book and Bowl, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Budget, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- C[ornell] U[niversity] L[ibraries] - Personal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Memos, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- [CUL] Serials Cataloguing, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- General - C-D-E, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Canadian Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- College Bowl, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Misc. European Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- European Acq. - Austria, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- European Acq. - Belgium, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- European Acq. - Denmark, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- European Acq. - England, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- European Acq. - France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- European Acq. - Germany, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Nardecchia, Jan. 1960-June 1960 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Nardecchia, July 1960-Dec. 1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- European Acq. - Italy, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- European Acq. - Netherlands, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- European Acq. - Spain, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- European Acq. - Switerland, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- General - F-G, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Gifts, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- General - H-I-J, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Harrassowitz, July 1960-Dec. 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Harrassowitz, Jan. 1960-June 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Isreali Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Kahn, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kraus, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Kraus, H.P., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- General - K-L, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- General - M, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- General - M, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Library of Congress - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Mr. Malott's Orders, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Microcard Committee, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Micro - Misc. Foreign, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Micro - England, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Foreign Microfilm Project, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Micro - University Micofilms, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Micro - United States, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Music Committee, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- General - N, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Nijhoff, Jan. 1960-June 1960 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Nijhoff, July 1960-Dec. 1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- N[ew] Y[ork] P[ublic] L[ibraries], 1960 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- General - O-P-Q-R, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Philippines Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Fr. Personal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Russian Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- General - S-T, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Serials Currently Received, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Central and South America, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Correspondence re Southeast Asian Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Echols, Memos, etc., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Russian Acquisitions, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- SEA Acquisitions - Misc., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- SEA Acquisitions - Japan, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Stechert, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- General - U-V-W, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- U.S. Acquisitions - A-Z, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Tice and Lynch, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- General - X-Y-Z, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- African Acquisitions, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- ALA, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- ALA Midwinter Conference, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Allen, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- America's Acquisitions, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Asian Acq. (PL 480), [1961]-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Australia, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Budget-Book Funds, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Canada Acquisitions, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- European Acquisitions - Austria-Denmark, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- European Acq. - England, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- European Acq. - France, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- European Acq. - Germany, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- European Acq. - Greece-Italy, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- European Acq. - Netherlands-Switzerland, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- European Acq. - Philippines, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- European Acq. - Russian, A-K, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- European Acq. - Russian, L-Z, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- French Want List, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Harrassowitz, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- History and Library Science Allerton House Conference, Sept. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Inter-Libaray Correspondence, A-Z, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Israel Acq., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Kaske, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Kraus, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Master Copies - Want List, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Micro - Orders, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Music Committee Dedication Concert, [1962]-1963 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Nijhoff, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Personal, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Personnel, 1959; 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Planning Committee Acquisitions, 1959; [1961-1963] (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Reclassification, 1961-[1962]-1963 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Russian Acquisitions, 1962-[1963] (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Russian Committee Meetings, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Sugar, Gold, and Coffee, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- U.S. Acquisitions, A-B, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- U.S. Acquisitions, C, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- U.S. Acquisitions, D-G, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- U.S. Acquisitions, H, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- U.S. Acquisitions, I-L, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- U.S. Acquisitions, M, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- U.S. Acquisitions, N-Q, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- U.S. Acquisitions, R, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- U.S. Acquisitions, S, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- U.S. Acquisitions, T-Z, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Want List - Apr. 1963, Kaske and Godolphin (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Washington University - Fr., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- "A", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- ACRL Prize, Competition, Rules, Draft, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- ACRL Microcard Committee: Letters to Deans of Library Schools re Master Thesis, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ALA Planning Committee, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- ALA Subscription Book Committee, 1956; [1963-1964] (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Allen, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- America's Acquisitions, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Annual Report: Uris Library, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Asian Acquisitions, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Austria-Denmark, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- "B", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Blancheteav, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- "C", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- The Catalog in European Libraries, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Catalog Policy, 1953; 1955,; 1957-1958,; 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Chow Huang Cora, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Columbia Univesity Library School, 1963-[1964] (Box 7, Folder 32)
- "D-E", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- England, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- "F", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- France, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- "G", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Germany, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Greece-Italy, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- "H", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Harrassowitz, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Helbring and Lichfenhahn, Hand L, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- "I-K", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Kraus, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "L", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Library Associates, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Library Association Donations, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- "M", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Microfilm, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Micro Orders, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Music Committee, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- "N", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Nardecchia, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Netherlands-Switzerland, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Nijhoff, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- "O-P", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Personal, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Personal Bills, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Fr. Personal Bills, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Research Club, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- "Q-R", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Fr. Review: Walford Guide...Supplement, for A-LA-SBB, Mar. 1964 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Fr. Reviews: Denton, German and American Univeristy Libraries, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Reichmann, Felix. "New Frontiers in Technical Services" (paper) (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Research Club, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Russian Acquisitions, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Russian Acquisitions: Fischer, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Russian Acquisitions: Pintner, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- "S", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Soviet Studies Meeting, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- "T", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Technical Services Administrators of Large Research Libraries, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Techincal Services: Directors of Large Research Libraries, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Tice and Lynch, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- "U", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- U.S., A-Z, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- "W-Y", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Yale, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- "Z", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Robert Champigny, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Gershoy, Leo, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Hockett's Lectures, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Humanities Council, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Humanities Council, 1957; 1959-[1960] (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Humanities Council, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Humanities Council, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Humanities Council, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Humanities Council, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Humanities Council, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Humanities Council, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- H[umanities] [Council], 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Humanities Council, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Humanities Council Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Humanities Council's Committees, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Humanities Council Lectures, 1959-[1960] (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Humanities Council Minutes, Reports, etc., 1960-[1961] (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Humanities Council Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Humanities Council Minutes and Agenda, 1963-[1964] (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Minutes of the Humanities Council, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Minutes of the Humanities Council, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Humanities Council: Correspondence and Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Humanities Council Minutes, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Humanities Council for Whiton Lectures, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Italian Lecture Fellowship (Fiske Dante - Petrarch Collections), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Nelson Goodman, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Leo Strauss, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- E. Wasserman, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Junior Whitons, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Junior Whitons, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Whitons, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Whiton Club Support, [1963]-1964 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Junior Whiton Lectures, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Whiton Lectures, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Whiton Lectures, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Whiton Lectures, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Rudolf Wittkower, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Walter Ullman, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Von Wright, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Notebook of Library Address All over the World (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Afganistan, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Africa, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Algeria (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Argentina (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Australia, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Austria, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Belgium, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Brazil, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Bulgaria, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Burma, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Cambodia, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Canada, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Ceylon, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- China, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Congo, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cuba (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Czechoslovakia, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Denmark, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Egypt, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Finland, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Formosa, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- France, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Germany, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Germany Bry, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Ghana, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Great Britain, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Greece, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Hong Kong, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Hungary, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Iceland, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- India, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Indonesia, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Iran, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Israel, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Italy, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Japan, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Korea, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Latin America, Misc., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Malaya, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Mexico (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Morocco (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Netherlands, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- New Zealand, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Norway, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Pakistan, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Panama, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Philippines, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Poland, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Portugal, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Puerto Rico (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Rumania (Box 10, Folder 52)
- South Africa, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Spain, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Sweden, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Switzerland, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Thailand, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Mr. Troiziji (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Turkey, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Union Catalogues, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- U.S.S.R., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Vietnam, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Yugoslavia, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Answers and Code Numbers (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Corrected Drafts of Article and Sources with Annotations (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Copy of Article, [1969]-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- European Replies, 1968-[1969] (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Paper by M.F. Tauber, "Types of Materials and Their Sources", 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Paper: Written Draft, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)